[
    {
        "question": "What is the population of South Korea?",
        "option1": "43 million",
        "option2": "48 million",
        "option3": "52 million",
        "option4": "57 million",
        "answer": "52 million"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is South Korea’s approximate fertility rate, a measure of the total births per a woman’s lifetime?",
        "option1": "1",
        "option2": "less than 1",
        "option3": "2",
        "option4": "3",
        "answer": "less than 1"
    },







    {
        "question": "At what year did Korea separate into South and North?",
        "option1": "1927",
        "option2": "1935",
        "option3": "1948",
        "option4": "1953",
        "answer": "1948"
    },













    {
        "question": "When eating with someone older than you, you should make sure you have the first bite.",
        "option1": "True",
        "option2": "False",
        "answer": "False"
    },

    {
        "question": "It’s important to give tips to taxi drivers in South Korea.",
        "option1": "True",
        "option2": "False",
        "answer": "False"
    },

    {
        "question": "When handing over/receiving object from strangers or someone older than you, you should use both hands.",
        "option1": "True",
        "option2": "False",
        "answer": "True"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the most common way Korean people greet one another?",
        "option1": "Bow",
        "option2": "Hug",
        "option3": "Rub noses",
        "option4": "Kiss on the cheek",
        "answer": "Bow"
    },

    {
        "question": "It’s rude to ask people’s ages on a first date.",
        "option1": "True",
        "option2": "False",
        "answer": "False"
    },

    {
        "question": "Writing someone’s name in red ink shows extra respect, love, and sincerity.",
        "option1": "True",
        "option2": "False",
        "answer": "False"
    },

    {
        "question": "What do Korean people typically do when attending someone’s wedding?",
        "option1": "Wear a leather bracelet to show respect for the bride & grooms’ parents",
        "option2": "Prepare some cash in an envelope for the bride & groom",
        "option3": "Bring a pink rose bouquet to decorate the bride’s waiting room",
        "option4": "Never take videos when the bride enters to show respect",
        "answer": "Prepare some cash in an envelope for the bride & groom"
    }
]